{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038586628","data":{"timestamp":" 947038586628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 6b7ad416-3948-4b0a-819c-b415fdc02c3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038592930","data":{"timestamp":" 947038592930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 6b7ad416-3948-4b0a-819c-b415fdc02c3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038593212","data":{"timestamp":" 947038593211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 6b7ad416-3948-4b0a-819c-b415fdc02c3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038598891","data":{"timestamp":" 947038598891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 6b7ad416-3948-4b0a-819c-b415fdc02c3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038607657","data":{"timestamp":" 947038607656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 6b7ad416-3948-4b0a-819c-b415fdc02c3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038619158","data":{"timestamp":" 947038619157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038619393","data":{"timestamp":" 947038619392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038620365","data":{"timestamp":" 947038620364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038621661","data":{"timestamp":" 947038621659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038624625","data":{"timestamp":" 947038624624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038625482","data":{"timestamp":" 947038625481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038625800","data":{"timestamp":" 947038625799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038627045","data":{"timestamp":" 947038627044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038630618","data":{"timestamp":" 947038630618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038631601","data":{"timestamp":" 947038631601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038631854","data":{"timestamp":" 947038631854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038632797","data":{"timestamp":" 947038632796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038635778","data":{"timestamp":" 947038635777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038636811","data":{"timestamp":" 947038636811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038636871","data":{"timestamp":" 947038636870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038636950","data":{"timestamp":" 947038636950"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038644224","data":{"timestamp":" 947038644224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 5b449070-f5f9-4a9b-b98a-947c8a1fc9f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038660334","data":{"timestamp":" 947038660334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_juma_wote-juma-wezi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" juma"," userResponse":" juma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038669486","data":{"timestamp":" 947038669486"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kima_duni-hoho-kima"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kima"," userResponse":" kima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038678735","data":{"timestamp":" 947038678735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_juma_juma-koti-naye"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" juma"," userResponse":" juma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038687659","data":{"timestamp":" 947038687659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_lako-mama-goli"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038698244","data":{"timestamp":" 947038698244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mama-dudu-yowe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" dudu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038709919","data":{"timestamp":" 947038709919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mama-dudu-yowe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mama"," userResponse":" mama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ma.noShow.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038715901","data":{"timestamp":" 947038715900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mama-dudu-yowe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038730704","data":{"timestamp":" 947038730703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mama-dudu-yowe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038743159","data":{"timestamp":" 947038743158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" e4728814-ee0f-44ee-bb09-d99a29384d85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ma.noShow.24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mama_mama-dudu-yowe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038761137","data":{"timestamp":" 947038761137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038762191","data":{"timestamp":" 947038762191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mlima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038768999","data":{"timestamp":" 947038768999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038770046","data":{"timestamp":" 947038770046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038780072","data":{"timestamp":" 947038780072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038781129","data":{"timestamp":" 947038781129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ngoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOMA"," userResponse":" NGOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038791760","data":{"timestamp":" 947038791760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nelima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038792811","data":{"timestamp":" 947038792811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nelima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NELIMA"," userResponse":" NELIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038801186","data":{"timestamp":" 947038801186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumuuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038802229","data":{"timestamp":" 947038802229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumuuma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUUMA"," userResponse":" KUMUUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038805799","data":{"timestamp":" 947038805799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038806840","data":{"timestamp":" 947038806840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038809961","data":{"timestamp":" 947038809961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hekima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038811000","data":{"timestamp":" 947038811000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hekima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEKIMA"," userResponse":" HEKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038815488","data":{"timestamp":" 947038815488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038816527","data":{"timestamp":" 947038816527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alisema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038822760","data":{"timestamp":" 947038822760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alinguruma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038823798","data":{"timestamp":" 947038823798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" alinguruma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINGURUMA"," userResponse":" ALINGURUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038831324","data":{"timestamp":" 947038831323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SELMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038832408","data":{"timestamp":" 947038832408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SELMA"," userResponse":" SELMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038836033","data":{"timestamp":" 947038836032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038836271","data":{"timestamp":" 947038836270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" f163ee17-15b6-432f-b202-0ff2878b0fbd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.ma.rand.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" selma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SELMA"," userResponse":" SELMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038847957","data":{"timestamp":" 947038847957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038848179","data":{"timestamp":" 947038848179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038849142","data":{"timestamp":" 947038849142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038850414","data":{"timestamp":" 947038850414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038852138","data":{"timestamp":" 947038852136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038852183","data":{"timestamp":" 947038852183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038858346","data":{"timestamp":" 947038858345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.ma.rand.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038865377","data":{"timestamp":" 947038865377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038872610","data":{"timestamp":" 947038872609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.na.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038880216","data":{"timestamp":" 947038880216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038893226","data":{"timestamp":" 947038893225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" dba19064-b937-40c4-8c42-3e65bb56d84d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038936596","data":{"timestamp":" 947038936596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038945981","data":{"timestamp":" 947038945981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pana_damu-pana-babu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pana"," userResponse":" pana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038955843","data":{"timestamp":" 947038955843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lina_lina-lako-moto"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lina"," userResponse":" lina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038966406","data":{"timestamp":" 947038966406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kina_kina-juma-kwao"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kina"," userResponse":" kina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038981108","data":{"timestamp":" 947038981108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947038990009","data":{"timestamp":" 947038990009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lina_lina-ndoo-yake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lina"," userResponse":" lina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039002887","data":{"timestamp":" 947039002887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039020982","data":{"timestamp":" 947039020982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aina_kale-lini-aina"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aina"," userResponse":" aina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039030222","data":{"timestamp":" 947039030222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_tano-hana-taji"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039047995","data":{"timestamp":" 947039047994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jona_jona-yenu-kinu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jona"," userResponse":" jona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039053762","data":{"timestamp":" 947039053761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" c189e52d-36f2-4c78-a2bb-a12f654a51d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_jona_jona-yenu-kinu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039080713","data":{"timestamp":" 947039080713"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kina_kina-juma-kwao"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kina"," userResponse":" kina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039101494","data":{"timestamp":" 947039101494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jona_jona-yenu-kinu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jona"," userResponse":" yenu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039111113","data":{"timestamp":" 947039111113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jona_jona-yenu-kinu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jona"," userResponse":" jona"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039122318","data":{"timestamp":" 947039122318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_tano-hana-taji"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039144204","data":{"timestamp":" 947039144204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pana_damu-pana-babu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pana"," userResponse":" pana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039160748","data":{"timestamp":" 947039160748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_adie-joto-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039179337","data":{"timestamp":" 947039179337"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039180488","data":{"timestamp":" 947039180487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039188761","data":{"timestamp":" 947039188760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039196615","data":{"timestamp":" 947039196615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039204679","data":{"timestamp":" 947039204679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039211967","data":{"timestamp":" 947039211967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039219347","data":{"timestamp":" 947039219347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039229551","data":{"timestamp":" 947039229551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" d6ded747-cd02-4dbf-af18-3db36a3ac880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039244094","data":{"timestamp":" 947039244094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 631654fb-77fc-4cbf-9aa2-50cd96fd90be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039255645","data":{"timestamp":" 947039255644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 631654fb-77fc-4cbf-9aa2-50cd96fd90be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039263416","data":{"timestamp":" 947039263416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 631654fb-77fc-4cbf-9aa2-50cd96fd90be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039272942","data":{"timestamp":" 947039272942"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 631654fb-77fc-4cbf-9aa2-50cd96fd90be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039283317","data":{"timestamp":" 947039283317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 631654fb-77fc-4cbf-9aa2-50cd96fd90be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_lini-kuna-kila"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039304993","data":{"timestamp":" 947039304993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pana_damu-pana-babu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pana"," userResponse":" pana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039327843","data":{"timestamp":" 947039327843"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lina_lina-ndoo-yake"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lina"," userResponse":" lina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039336310","data":{"timestamp":" 947039336310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_aina_kale-lini-aina"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" aina"," userResponse":" aina"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039349653","data":{"timestamp":" 947039349653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_tano-hana-taji"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039380332","data":{"timestamp":" 947039380332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.na.show.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039381249","data":{"timestamp":" 947039381248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..20.off2.16__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039404059","data":{"timestamp":" 947039404058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.show.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039413286","data":{"timestamp":" 947039413285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039419083","data":{"timestamp":" 947039419083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.ni.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039426012","data":{"timestamp":" 947039426012"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" ce7d20be-81b8-4033-90cf-201c804dc055"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.na.show.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_huku-yuko-tuna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039440356","data":{"timestamp":" 947039440356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039447195","data":{"timestamp":" 947039447195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039453596","data":{"timestamp":" 947039453596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039462140","data":{"timestamp":" 947039462139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039470567","data":{"timestamp":" 947039470567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039479229","data":{"timestamp":" 947039479229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039486538","data":{"timestamp":" 947039486538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039493038","data":{"timestamp":" 947039493038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039503825","data":{"timestamp":" 947039503825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039511286","data":{"timestamp":" 947039511286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039514812","data":{"timestamp":" 947039514812"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039519400","data":{"timestamp":" 947039519400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039529625","data":{"timestamp":" 947039529625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039538127","data":{"timestamp":" 947039538127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039545825","data":{"timestamp":" 947039545824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039555666","data":{"timestamp":" 947039555666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039561526","data":{"timestamp":" 947039561525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 74a801e7-e28f-495a-8e83-c72c08dbbbae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039598123","data":{"timestamp":" 947039598123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_yadi-jani-maua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039617090","data":{"timestamp":" 947039617090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_pana-nani-lori"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039645771","data":{"timestamp":" 947039645770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pini_jitu-pini-isha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pini"," userResponse":" pini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039674708","data":{"timestamp":" 947039674708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_jani-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039688891","data":{"timestamp":" 947039688890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuni_elsa-kuni-mbao"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuni"," userResponse":" kuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039703748","data":{"timestamp":" 947039703748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_geni_geni-kumi-jike"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" geni"," userResponse":" jike"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039714246","data":{"timestamp":" 947039714246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_geni_geni-kumi-jike"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" geni"," userResponse":" geni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039724362","data":{"timestamp":" 947039724362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tani_tani-lala-vuta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tani"," userResponse":" tani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039748936","data":{"timestamp":" 947039748936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nani_mara-nani-tele"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nani"," userResponse":" nani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039757502","data":{"timestamp":" 947039757501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jani_neno-yetu-jani"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jani"," userResponse":" jani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039767541","data":{"timestamp":" 947039767541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ni.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039771745","data":{"timestamp":" 947039771744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039779435","data":{"timestamp":" 947039779435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 54935783-c4e4-47d8-95e7-f093110c25c4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.ni.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nini_kato-nini-kata"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039808602","data":{"timestamp":" 947039808602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039810210","data":{"timestamp":" 947039810210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039821534","data":{"timestamp":" 947039821534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039830833","data":{"timestamp":" 947039830833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039855588","data":{"timestamp":" 947039855587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039867658","data":{"timestamp":" 947039867658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039878514","data":{"timestamp":" 947039878514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 02344838-de8a-4895-af87-e05e32368407"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039894049","data":{"timestamp":" 947039894049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039910448","data":{"timestamp":" 947039910448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039929438","data":{"timestamp":" 947039929438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039940835","data":{"timestamp":" 947039940834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039946390","data":{"timestamp":" 947039946390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039970569","data":{"timestamp":" 947039970569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039980995","data":{"timestamp":" 947039980995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039982466","data":{"timestamp":" 947039982466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039998206","data":{"timestamp":" 947039998206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039999313","data":{"timestamp":" 947039999313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.ni.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040008655","data":{"timestamp":" 947040008655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040033511","data":{"timestamp":" 947040033511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" eb6b48b4-52a8-4639-a22e-2e673e5b7339"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.ni.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___ni"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040047953","data":{"timestamp":" 947040047953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040050895","data":{"timestamp":" 947040050895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040053273","data":{"timestamp":" 947040053273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040056440","data":{"timestamp":" 947040056439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040059653","data":{"timestamp":" 947040059653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040062625","data":{"timestamp":" 947040062625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040065765","data":{"timestamp":" 947040065765"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kabisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040069952","data":{"timestamp":" 947040069952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elsa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELSA"," userResponse":" ELSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040072870","data":{"timestamp":" 947040072870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040075968","data":{"timestamp":" 947040075967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.sa.rand.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040079404","data":{"timestamp":" 947040079404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040079601","data":{"timestamp":" 947040079597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" 16aad101-e1b2-4ae1-8d96-ada440346121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.sa.rand.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040103023","data":{"timestamp":" 947040103023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" bdd0b714-f009-4677-a742-26587cd6475f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040112175","data":{"timestamp":" 947040112175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" bdd0b714-f009-4677-a742-26587cd6475f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040117820","data":{"timestamp":" 947040117820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" bdd0b714-f009-4677-a742-26587cd6475f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040133756","data":{"timestamp":" 947040133755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" bdd0b714-f009-4677-a742-26587cd6475f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040142204","data":{"timestamp":" 947040142204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_051603"," gameId":" bdd0b714-f009-4677-a742-26587cd6475f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}